export const vocabulary = [
    { question: 'α', answer: 'alpha' },
    { question: 'β', answer: 'beta' },
    { question: 'γ', answer: 'gamma' },
    { question: 'δ', answer: 'delta' },
    { question: 'ε', answer: 'epsilon' },

    { question: 'ζ', answer: 'zeta' },
    { question: 'η', answer: 'eta' },
    { question: 'θ', answer: 'theta' },
    { question: 'ι', answer: 'iota' },
    { question: 'κ', answer: 'kappa' },

    { question: 'λ', answer: 'lambda' },
    { question: 'μ', answer: 'mu' },
    { question: 'ν', answer: 'nu' },
    { question: 'ξ', answer: 'xi' },
    { question: 'ο', answer: 'omicron' },

    { question: 'π', answer: 'pi' },
    { question: 'ρ', answer: 'rho' },
    { question: 'σ, ς', answer: 'sigma' },
    { question: 'τ', answer: 'tau' },
    { question: 'υ', answer: 'upsilon' },

    { question: 'φ', answer: 'phi' },
    { question: 'χ', answer: 'chi' },
    { question: 'ψ', answer: 'psi' },
    { question: 'ω', answer: 'omega' },
];